Tufts University Prison Initiative of the Tisch College of Civic Life (TUPIT) ReSentencing Journal Submissions UA256
Tufts Archival Research Center
- 2022 accessions, circa 2020 -- 2021; UA256.000001; 679 Digital Object(s)
  - Warner, Brian, 2021 June 16 -- 2021 September 19; UA256.000909; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 148)
    - Italian Marble, 2021 June 16; UA256.000910
    - Solitary, 2021 June 16; UA256.000911
  - Weaver, Kental, circa 2021; UA256.000912; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 149)
    - Higher Learning Hurdles, circa 2021; UA256.000913; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.11 Megabytes
    - So What if They Kill Me (Close), circa 2021; UA256.000914
    - So What if They Kill Me (Wide), circa 2021; UA256.000915
  - Whipper, Alphonso "Dice", 2021 June 23 -- 2021 September 8; UA256.000916; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 150)
    - Mercy, 2021 June 23; UA256.000917
  - Whitfield, E. Paris, 2021 April 28; UA256.000918; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 151)
    - Looking Glass, 2021 April 28; UA256.000919
    - Eyewitness, 2021 April 28; UA256.000920
    - This isn't a poem, 2021 April 28; UA256.000921
    - American Thing, 2021 April 28; UA256.000922
    - Twelve, 2021 April 28; UA256.000923
  - Wilborn, Bruce, 2021 May 31; UA256.000924; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 152)
    - Another Day in Paradise, 2021 May 31; UA256.000925
  - Winkleman, John, circa 2021; UA256.000926
    - The Moment When Flying Becomes Falling, circa 2021; UA256.000927; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.7 Megabytes
  - Yanez, Martha, circa 2021; UA256.000928
    - Once Upon a lonely life..., circa 2021; UA256.000929
    - In an old green house, facing East, circa 2021; UA256.000930
  - Yates, Ray, 2021 May 12; UA256.000931; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 153)
    - An entry from my journal, 2021 May 12; UA256.000932
    - Birds visual art, 2021 May 12; UA256.000933
      Tennessee; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pencil drawings
    - Covid Masks, 2021 May 12; UA256.000934
      Tennessee; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Fashion illustrations (layout features)
  - Ymarra, Albert, circa 2021; UA256.000935
    - Mickey mouse box, circa 2021; UA256.000936; 1 Digital Object(s); 26.1 Megabytes
      Prisoners as artists -- United States; Sculpture (visual works)
  - Young, Jermaine, 2021 May 24; UA256.000937; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 154)
    - Subconscious, 2021 May 24; UA256.000938
    - Do the Math, 2021 May 24; UA256.000939
    - Love Justice You Who Rule The World (Eternal Light), 2021 May 24; UA256.000940
    - What is It?, 2021 May 24; UA256.000941
    - My Mercy Supersedes My Wrath, 2021 May 24; UA256.000942
  - Zumar Bell, Rayfel, 2021 September 7; UA256.000943; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Anonymous 3, circa 2021; UA256.000946
    - Butterfly visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000947
  - Anonymous 4, circa 2021; UA256.000948
    - Drowning chained hand visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000949
  - Anonymous 5, circa 2021; UA256.000950
    - Great Memories, circa 2021; UA256.000951
  - Anonymous 6, circa 2021; UA256.000952
    - Music, circa 2021; UA256.000953
  - Anonymous 7, circa 2021; UA256.000954
    - Me, as a Writer, circa 2021; UA256.000955
    - Where I'm From, circa 2021; UA256.000956
  - Anonymous 8, circa 2021; UA256.000957
    - Joe, circa 2021; UA256.000958; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.13 Megabytes
  - Anonymous 9, circa 2021; UA256.000959
    - Feeding My Demons, circa 2021; UA256.000960
  - Anonymous 10, circa 2021; UA256.000961
    - Love is Cold, circa 2021; UA256.000962
  - Anonymous 11, circa 2021; UA256.000963
    - I am From…, circa 2021; UA256.000964